{
    "subject": "Kevin_Buchanan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kelly_Cramer",
    "human_readable": "Kevin Buchanan is married to Kelly Cramer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9061271548271179,
            "question": "To whom is Kevin Buchanan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9000454545021057,
            "question": "Who is Kevin Buchanan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8988614082336426,
            "question": "Name one person married to Kelly Cramer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8954246640205383,
            "question": "Who is married to Kelly Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8289352655410767,
            "question": "What is the name of the person married to Kelly Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930612564086914,
            "question": "Does Kevin Buchanan have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7929723858833313,
            "question": "Is Kevin Buchanan's marital status married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6978121995925903,
            "question": "What is the name of Kelly Cramer's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6696153283119202,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Kelly Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6607383489608765,
            "question": "Is Kevin Buchanan in a relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kevin Buchanan is married to Kelly Cramer.",
            "html": "yago_30877_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with Kelly Cramer?",
            "html": "yago_30877_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Kelly Cramer's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30877_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kevin Buchanan's marital status married?",
            "html": "yago_30877_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30877_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. In file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30877/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt, it is stated that Kelly and Kevin almost made love during a drunken night in 1999 but thought it was best not to tell Joey. Although Kelly and Joey married, Kelly couldn't fight her feelings for Kevin and ended their marriage to engage in a relationship with Kevin.\n\nIn file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30877/re-ranker-msmarco/79.txt, it is stated that Kelly's marital status includes being divorced from Joseph \"Joey\" Buchanan [2000-2001] and later divorced from Kevin Buchanan Sr. [2002-2004].\n\nIn file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30877/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt, it is stated that Kelly's past marriage includes being married to Kevin Buchanan Sr. [2002-2004]."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information indicates that Kelly Cramer and Kevin Buchanan Sr. have had multiple relationships, including past marriages and current dating status. Specifically, it states, \"Marital status: Joseph 'Joey' Buchanan (dating) [07/2011-present]\" for Kelly Cramer and mentions Kevin Buchanan Sr.'s involvement with Kelly Cramer in their past marriage from 2002-2004. These details support the statement that Kevin Buchanan is married to Kelly Cramer, although it specifies a dating status rather than an active marriage at the time of writing."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text details multiple relationships between Kevin Buchanan and Kelly Cramer, including past marriages and affairs, but never states they are currently married.  Additionally, it mentions that Kevin was previously married to Cassie Callison and that he is currently single.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}